[{"id": 3129, "question": "WASHINGTON, Sept. 6 (Xinhua) -- U.S. President Barack Obama on Monday announced a new plan to renew and expand the nation's roads, railways and runways, in a bid to restart the _ economy and to help create jobs. Obama announced the billion-dollar infrastructure spending program at an event in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, marking the Labor Day holiday in the United States. The proposal calls for investments over six years, including rebuilding and modernizing 150,000 miles (241,350 kilometers) of roads, 4,000 miles (6,430 kilometers) of railways and 150 miles ( 241 kilometers) of runways. \"It sets up an Infrastructure Bank to leverage(;) federal dollars and focus on the smartest investment. All of this will not only create jobs now, but will make our economy run better over the long haul,\" Obama s...\n\nQ: What's the main idea of this passage?", "options": ["The US president launched a new program aiming at improving the nation's infrastructure.", "The US unemployment rate rose according to the Labor Department.", "These years will be the most difficult in the American history.", "More roads, railways and runways will be rebuilt and modernized."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2818, "question": "When someone meets a stranger with the same hobby, that person immediately becomes a friend. People enjoy the company of others who share a similar interest. Often they will form a club and travel great distances to attend meetings where they can talk about their hobbies. Other people have such unusual hobbies that no one else can share them. Sometimes they try to do something better, faster or longer than anyone else in order to have their names included in the Guinness Book of World Records. A lady in Massachusetts may have the world's easiest hobby; she let her hair grow. Diane Witt has not cut her hair for twelve years. It is now eight feet (2.44 meters) long, and she will soon set a new world record and her name will be placed in the Guinness Book. A thirty-year-old man in Pennsylvani...\n\nQ: From the passage we know that_.", "options": ["sometimes people try to do something better, faster or longer than anyone else to have their names included in the Guinness Book of World Records", "a lady in New York hasn't cut her hair for twelve years", "a teacher in Massachusetts typed for over 162 hours", "a lady from Iowa spend six months typing the numbers from one to one million"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2073, "question": "High Speed Book Scanner Simply turning pages of a book quickly may not seem like the best way to scan it. A Japanese research group at Tokyo University has created new software that allows hundreds of pages to be scanned within minutes. Scanning text is normally a boring process with each page having to be inserted into a scanner, but the team led by Professor Masatoshi Ishikawa uses a high speed camera that takes 500 pictures a second to scan pages as they are turned by workers. Normal scanners can only scan the information that is actually before them on the page. This high speed book scanner uses a camera that captures pages at 1000fps as they are turned. A system built in allows it to automatically correct any changes to the text due to the page bending as well as light differences due...\n\nQ: According to the passage, the advantage of the new scanning software is that    _   .", "options": ["there is no need to scan every page", "it can work much more effectively", "no manpower is needed in operating the scanner", "it can make the scanning process more interesting"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2419, "question": "Recently I have discovered it's often easier for me to do something every day than to do it just some days. I post to my blog six days a week. I take notes every day. I write in my one-sentence journal every day. Many people have told me that they find it easier to exercise when they exercise every day. If I try to do something just four days a week, I spend a lot of time arguing with myself: Is today the day, or is it tomorrow, or the next day? Does the week start on Sunday or Monday? If you do something every day, you tend to fall into a routine. Routine has a bad reputation for lacking excitement. It's true that novelty and challenge bring happiness and that people who break their routines, try new things, and go to new places are happier, but I think that some routine activities also b...\n\nQ: People usually tend to break their routines because they  _  .", "options": ["hope to have a better reputation", "would like to get rid of the old habit", "want to have fun and excitement", "are willing to face new challenges"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 271, "question": "Coral reefs are not just beautiful to look at,but also very useful.They shelter nearly 25% of ocean life and provide food for billions of people.However, like many other species,this amazing ecosystem is in danger of dying out! There are two main reasons for the destruction--the rising carbon dioxide levels caused by global warming as well as human influences like bottom operation.While not much can be done about the former,the loss caused by the latter can be reduced. Bottom operation involves dropping nets to the ocean bed and then dragging them up when filled with fish.This action damaged the ocean floor,causing the coral branches to separate from the reefs.While that is very discouraging,the good news is that if these branches are found quickly,they can be saved.At present,that work is...\n\nQ: Which of the following is a cause of the danger that coral reefs are facing?", "options": ["The appearance of new creatures.", "The seriously polluted sea water.", "The activities of volunteer divers.", "Human activities like bottom operation."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1136, "question": "The slogan \"a dog is for life, not just for Christmas\" has been going strong for 27 years now. Dogs and cats have been popular Christmas gifts in the gifts in the UK and Europe for many years. But some people still haven't quite got the message. The slogan still holds good. Some 105,000 dogs were _ by local government last year because they had been abandoned, many of them shortly after the festival season. The main reason given by owners for handing their dogs over to the Dogs Trust is that the dogs need more attention than they can give; behavioral problems and moving home are also reasons given. But Eleanor Silk, the Trust's communications director, says, \"It's often four or five months after Christmas, in early summer, when owners find that the dog has got too big and too active, or it...\n\nQ: Why is the author against the idea of putting a dog in the Christmas stocking as a Christmas gift?", "options": ["Because these dogs can still cause damage.", "Because children will not take dogs seriously.", "Because children don't like to have dogs as Christmas gifts.", "Because a Christmas stocking is not big enough to put a dog in."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3474, "question": "When his book Little Princes begins, Conor Grennan is planning a year-long trip around the globe, a journey that began with a three-month volunteer service at the Little Princes Children's home, an orphanage in Nepal. When he arrived at the orphanage, Conor was immediately welcomed by all the children even though he had no previous experience in working with children. He quickly grew to love the job. But it wasn't long before Conor came to learn that the children were not orphans at all -- they were actually children who had been separated from their parents by a child trafficker . This realization turned Conor's global journey into a strong desire to try to find a way to reunite these children with their families. As a part of his efforts, Conor did a great amount of work when he was back...\n\nQ: What do we know about Little Princes Children's Home?", "options": ["It is a profitable organization.", "The children in it are all orphans.", "It has many branches all over Nepal.", "Many children ended up there due to illegal trade."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2077, "question": "The United States government has decided that food from cloned cattle, pigs and goats is safe to eat. The Food and Drug Administration also says it found no risks in meat and milk from cloned animals. The F.D.A. looked at studies for several years before it announced its decision in a final report this month. The United States Department of Agriculture supported the findings. But it says time is needed to clear the way for marketing meat and milk from clones. The F.D.A. will not require any product to be registered as coming from clones. A producer would need to label a product \"clone-free\". The agency says that could be misunderstood because the food is not different from other food. But activists argue that the F.D.A. based its decision on incomplete research into possible risks. The Cen...\n\nQ: All the following are sure of the safety of cloned products EXCEPT   _  .", "options": ["New Zealand", "Japan", "the USA", "the European Union"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1815, "question": "I want to tell you a story that changed my life many years ago. We were living in College Station, Texas and my wife and I were on our way home from Houston, Texas one Saturday morning. We decided to stop at a local restaurant to get something to eat since we had enough time. When we finished, we got back into our car and before I started it, we noticed a homeless man standing in front of the building. His clothes were worn and it looked as though he didn't have any money. It was cold and I was sure he wanted something warm to drink; however, it was not this that I remember, because that is not what \"moved\" me. A dog was also walking up to the front of the building. Being a dog owner, I knew that the dog was a mother, and that she had just had some pups . She was hungry and weak and I felt...\n\nQ: Where did the story happen?", "options": ["In front of the local restaurant.", "In front of a building.", "In the car parking lot.", "Near the author's house."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1541, "question": "Ban Fur? Then Why Not Leather? Much to the displeasure of some local businesses, the City Council in West Hollywood, California, voted without opposition last week to ban the sale of fur products. Should laws be involved in this issue? Is it unfair to ban sales of fur, but not sales of leather and hides ? Animals Do Not Have Rights By Tibor R. Machan My view is that animals do not have basic rights. It is a matter of ethics and not of the laws of human societies. If animals had such rights as human beings do, they would have to be held responsible for killing fellow animals in the wild. That way of thinking about animals makes a category mistake. Using animals, including their fur or organs, to improve people's lives is acceptable. A Small Step Against Cruelty By Kate Carter Both fur and l...\n\nQ: Tibor R. Machan seems to believe that  _  .", "options": ["laws should be passed to protect animals", "humans are respornsible for killing animals", "it is not reasonable to use animals to improve life", "animals and humans aren't supposed to share equal rights"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2843, "question": "I want to let you know about an event that changed my life many years ago. We were living in College Station, Texas and my wife and I were on our way home from Houston, Texas one Sunday morning. We decided to stop at a local gas station to get something to eat since we had enough time. When we finished, we got back into our car and before I started it, we noticed a homeless man standing in front of the building. His clothes were worn and it looked as if he didn't have any money. It was cold and I was sure he wanted something to drink. However, it was not this that moved me. A dog was also walking up to the front of the building. Being a dog lover, I noticed that the dog was a mother and that she had just had some puppies . She was hungry and weak and I felt so bad for her. I knew if she di...\n\nQ: Which of the following moved the author?", "options": ["Most people walking by the dog didn't notice her", "The homeless man wore worn clothes on the cold day", "The homeless man bought food for the dog with all of his money", "The homeless man had not any money to buy any food for himself"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2152, "question": "With thousands of waterfalls across the world, it is difficult to choose the best but the following list contains some of the world's most amazing and beautiful ones! Iguazu Falls-The Iguazu Falls is located on the border of Brazil and Argentina and it is well-known for its scenic beauty. Though it is just about 89 meters high, it ranks as the fourth best waterfall in the world because of its beauty. The U-shaped cliff in the waterfall which is known as the Devil's throat is the most striking feature of the waterfall. Angel Falls-The Angel Falls, named after its discoverer James Crawford Angel, is the world's highest waterfalls, falling from a height of 979 meters. It is located in the Bolivar state in Venezuela. A unique feature of the falls is that most of the water falling down gets blo...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE about the Rhine Falls?", "options": ["It belongs to both Switzerland and German.", "It is the most beautiful waterfalls in the world.", "It possibly has a history of about 17,000 years.", "It falls off from the highest place in the world."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 505, "question": "Now some women are spending a weekend at Mother's Camp . There, husbands and children are not allowed. Why would a woman want to take a vacation without her family? Some women say they need time to be alone. At Mother's Camp a woman has room to herself. She can sleep, read or watch TV, and no one will bother her. No children will ask,\"Mom, what's for dinner?\" No husband will say, \"Oh, dear, I can't find any clean socks.\"In fact almost 50% of women in the United States work outside the home. Many of them work full-time and then come home to a second job-taking care of their homes and families. These working women say one of their biggest problems is housework. In the United States, working wives do about 75% of the housework. Many of their husbands say they want to help. But then they burn ...\n\nQ: What's the best title for this passage?", "options": ["Busy Working Mothers", "The US family", "Mothers Relax Away from Home", "Mothers in the US"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2013, "question": "Japan' s nuclear crisis is also causing concerns in China. Worried shoppers rushed to stores and supermarkets in the country for salt, with the belief that it might protect them from potential nuclear radiation spreading from Japan. Many rushed to buy to store as much iodized salt as possible because of the rumor that iodized salt could help prevent radiation poisoning spreading from Japan' s Fukushima Daiichi power plant. Consumers also worried that the nuclear plumes might spread to China by air and sea, polluting food sources, including salt taken from the sea. The wave of panic buying spread quickly across the country, driving up salt prices by five to ten fold in some cities. Even regions rich in salt production, like Jiangxi Province,faced sudden shortages. The government took measur...\n\nQ: What is the purpose of the writer to give the example of Beijing Salt Industry Corporation?", "options": ["To tell readers that there is a salt company in Beijing.", "To make people b elieve that the supply of salt is enough.", "To cal l on panic people to buy enough salt.", "To prove what the government did was right."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 947, "question": "Recipients of this year's Annenberg scholarships were announced on June 19. Brittany Blythe was one of them. In seventh grade,Brittany Blythe dreamed of being a cheerleader . Her school's coaches were less than enthusiastic. \"They said. 'I don't know how you'll be able to do it'. \"she recalls. \"'You won't be able to do it'.\" But Brittany,now a junior at Strath Haven High School near Philadelphia,refused to give up. And when the junior school cheerleaders won a tournament last year, she was right there,dancing and cheering with the rest of the team. Not bad for someone whose legs were cut off below the knee when she was two years old. Brittany,18,was born without shinbones --\"just blood and muscle tissue,\"as she puts it. When she tried to walk, her legs twisted. After the operation, she ada...\n\nQ: What does Brittany want to achieve at the moment?", "options": ["To stop others'laughing at her.", "To prove her coaches wrong.", "To remove her prostheses.", "To be a flyer."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1981, "question": "UNICEF reports that 40 million children below the age of 15 suffer from abuse and neglect. The USA National Committee to Prevent Child Abuse finds 3 million new reports of child abuse or neglect every year. According to such information on human rights abuses of children, the United Nations declared 2010 as the International Year of Youth. In answer to the common human rights abuses of young people, Dr. Mary Shuttleworth of Youth for Human Rights International(YHRI) recently completed her seventh annual World Tour to five continents in eighty days. The purpose of the tour is to promote the to tens of thousands of children and officials. According to UNICEF, 1.2 million children are illegally traded all over the world every year. Sold as goods, these children are forced into inhuman labor, ...\n\nQ: Youth for Human Rights International is paying attention to education because    _   .", "options": ["education should serve most children", "too many children are forced to leave school", "children who know their rights will make more money", "children who know little about their rights are easily cheated"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1742, "question": "\"Colour\" and \"color1\" , \"favourite\" and \"favorite\"\"- Have you ever wondered why Americans spell those words without a \"u\"? Is it because they are lazy? Of course not.In fact, the difference in spelling was created by Noah Webster(1758--1843) .He is a teacher who reformed English to make American identity stronger.Linguists celebrated his 250th birthday on October 16,2008.After the Revolutionary War(1775--1783) , Webster believed that Americans should have their own dictionary, rather than rely on British versions.He dropped the British \"u\" in some words.And he changed \"centre\" into \"center\" for children to learn English by spelling words more like they sounded. Webster wasn't shy about expressing his opinions.In defining preposterous (unreasonable) , he wrote: \"A Republican government in t...\n\nQ: According to the passage, when he worked on his dictionary, Noah Webster did all of the          following EXCEPT   _  .", "options": ["dropping \"u\" in all the British words", "changing \"centre\" into \"center\"", "adding local words", "voicing his opinion"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2735, "question": "We experience different forms of the Sun's energy every day. We can see its light and feel its warmth. The Sun is the major source of energy for our planet. It causes the evaporation of water from the oceans and lakes. Sunlight also provides the energy used by green plants to make their own food. These green plants then provide food for all organisms on the Earth. Much of the energy that comes from the Sun never reaches the Earth's surface. It is either reflected or absorbed by the gases in the upper atmosphere. Of the energy that reaches the lower atmosphere,30% is reflected by clouds or the Earth's surface. The remaining 70% warms the surface of the planet, causes water to evaporate, and provides energy for the water cycle and weather. Only a tiny part, approximately 0.023%, is actually ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, the root( ) cause for weather changes on the Earth is  _  .", "options": ["the atmosphere surrounding the Earth", "water from oceans and lakes", "energy from the Sun", "greenhouse gases in the sky"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2550, "question": "More than 4 in 10 cancers -- 600,000 in the UK alone -- could be prevented if people led healthier lives, say experts. The population of the UK is about 63,000,000. Latest figures from Cancer Research UK show smoking is the biggest avoidable risk factor , followed by unhealthy diets. The charity advises people to live healthily, limit alcohol intake and do regular exercise. According to the figures from 2007 to 2011, more than 300,000 cases of cancer recorded were linked to smoking. A further 145,000 were linked to unhealthy diets containing too much processed food. Obesity contributed to 88,000 cases and alcohol to 62,200. Sun damage to the skin and physical inactivity were also contributing factors. Professor Max Parkin, a Cancer Research UK statistician, says, \"There's now little doubt ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the third biggest avoidable cancer factor?", "options": ["Obesity.", "Alcohol intake.", "Unhealthy diets.", "Physical inactivity."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2320, "question": "One of the most famous basketball-players in the New Castle's history was paralyzed in a wheelchair one day...and was walking the next. Citizens of New Castle simply refer to it as \"The Miracle\". Joel Haler woke up in his dorm room at Hope College last October totally paralyzed from the waist down. Four hospitals later, the only way he could walk was through Robotic Walking Treatment. \"This past Tuesday, I was doing the Robotic walk and lasted ten minutes,\" Joel said. After that, he gave up. Joel wanted to accept the inevitable and cancelled his next Robotic Walking Treatment appointment. Then, the night before his cancelled appointment, he woke up to a terrible pain. An hour and a half later, the serious pain left him with an unusual feeling in his legs. \"As it continued to move up my leg...\n\nQ: According to the passage, \"The Miracle\" is that_.", "options": ["Joel Haler became the most famous basketball player", "Robotic Walking Treatment could cure paralysis", "Joel Haler could walk again after three months' paralysis", "a paralyzed boy could play basketball well"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 938, "question": "Shoppers who have cut back on purchases in the worrying U.S. economy are likely to continue their conservative shopping habits even if the economy improves, according to a new study. That signals continued bad news for retailers , who have been struggling to respond to a great cutback in spending as consumers have opened their wallets only for basic items, while cutting back on unimportant purchases. The report, which estimates retail sales growth to be flat this year, found that three-quarters of respondents to a monthly survey of 4,000 consumers said they had shifted their shopping behaviors because of the economy. Most said they were making do with less or going without some favorite items. \"The habits learned during this economic crisis have the potential to permanently change the mind...\n\nQ: Which is the measure the retailers won't take to attract shoppers?", "options": ["Adding more stores to the busy retail landscape.", "Keeping the editions of products limited.", "Making \"one-stop\" shops for customers.", "Concentrating on private brands and downsizing."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3290, "question": "From a very early age, some children show better self-control than others. Now, a new study that began with about 1,000 children in New Zealand has tracked how a child's low self-control can predict poor health, money troubles and even a criminal record in their adult years. Researchers have been studying this group of children for decades now. They observed the level of self-control the youngsters displayed. Parents, teachers, even the kids themselves, scored the youngsters on measures like \"acting before thinking\" and \"Persistence in reaching goals.\" The study led by Moffitt of Duke University and colleagues followed 1,000 children from birth to age 32 in Dunedin, New Zealand. \"The children who had the lowest self-control when they were age three to ten, later on had the most health prob...\n\nQ: Which of the following might be the best title of the  passage?", "options": ["Child's self-control predicts future health and success", "Kids are encouraged to take risks at an early age", "Children's development cannot be changed by teachers", "How to teach the kids a bit of self-control in schools"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1579, "question": "On a hot summer day, a soft drink can really take away your thirst. At home, at school, in the park or at the movies---you can find one almost anywhere. Carbonated You can see bubbles in these! Of all soft drinks sold, about 75 percent are carbonated . But be careful, carbonated soft drinks have lots of sugar and caffeine . Caffeine is not very good for you in the summer because it takes water out of your body. And the sugar can make you overweight if you drink too much. Fruit juice There are different kinds of juice. One kind is made only from fresh fruit. This kind of fruit juice may not taste sweet enough for some people, but it is nutritious . Another kind of fruit juice tastes good but has lots of sugar in it. Many young people buy this kind because the advertisements are good. It is ...\n\nQ: Which one may lead to your heart disease?", "options": ["Carbonated.", "Fruit juice.", "Energy drinks.", "Sports drinks"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1695, "question": "How words came into being is unknown. All we assume is that some early men invented certain sounds,in one way or another,to express thoughts and feelings,actions and things,so that they could talk with each other. Later they agreed upon certain signs,called letters,which could be put together to show those sounds,and which could be written down. Those sounds,whether spoken or written in letters, are called words. The power of words,then,lies in their associations--the things they bring up to our minds. Words become filled with meaning for us by experience;and the longer we live,the more certain words bring back to us the happy and sad events of our past;and the more we read and learn,the more the number of words that mean something to us increases. Great writers are those who not only have...\n\nQ: We learn from the text that language might have begun with  _  .", "options": ["expressions", "actions", "signs", "sounds"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3285, "question": "Nigel received a reward for his excellence in study. It began when he was selected to help the teachers in the computer laboratories. The peak of his school career came not when he topped the school but when he was selected for the nationwide competition. Unlike everyone else, Nigel wanted to join the contest because he liked making something out of the Lego sets. Nigel spent the next two months rebuilding the robot. It was during the time that Nigel found out about the prizes for the competition as well as another competitor, Alicia, from a neighboring school. His early intentions were forgotten. Getting the thousand-dollar prize was more important than anything else. Nigel decided to befriend Alicia. Unaware of his intentions, she told him all about the robot that she had been building f...\n\nQ: Why did Nigel help Alicia finish her robot?", "options": ["He tried to make friends with her", "He was fond of building robots", "He intended to help her", "He didn't want her to suspect him"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2647, "question": "Are you a creative person? Are you looking for a challenging and unique work environment? Picture yourself at CRIENGLISH.com Positions open to native English Speakers Only Video reporters/editors: 1. Video editing experience with an understanding of Final Cut Pro software. 2. Resourceful and creative when it comes to finding original stories. 3. A comfortable demeanor in front of the camera. 4. Enjoy working with others in a team oriented environment. News presenters: 1. Journalistic and radio experience, good news-writing skills. 2. Able to work the night and early morning shifts. 3. Team spirit and flexibility. Biz News Reporter/Presenter: 1. Journalistic experience, particularly in the field of business news. 2. Good reading and presentation skills. 3. Able to work at irregular hours. C...\n\nQ: Which of the following positions require irregular work hours?", "options": ["Video reporters&News presenters", "News presenters&Biz News Reporter", "Biz News Reporter&Copyeditors", "Copyeditors&Music DJs"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3131, "question": "I still remember my first day at school in London and I was half-excited and half-frightened. On my way to school I wondered what sort of questions the other boys would ask me and practiced all the answers: \"I am nine years old. I was born here but I haven't lived here since I was two. I was living in Farley. It's about thirty miles away. I came back to London two months ago.\" I also wondered if it was the custom for boys to fight strangers like me, but I was tall for my age. I hoped they would decide not to risk it. No one took any notice of me before school. I stood in the center of the playground, expecting someone to say \"hello\", but no one spoke to me. When a teacher called my name and told me where my classroom was, one or two boys looked at me but that was all. My teacher was called...\n\nQ: The writer prepared to answer all of the following questions EXCEPT \"  _  \".", "options": ["How old are you?", "Where are you from?", "Do you want to join my gang?", "When did you come back to London?"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2480, "question": "We live in a dangerous world. The figures for crime go up year by year. If you were attacked in the street, would you be able to defend yourself? Not very well probably, especially if someone was pointing a gun at you. We all see a lot of violence of films, but recently some programs on television showed how people can defend themselves without guns. For example, in one film a woman was attacked from behind. She threw the man, who was heavier and stronger than she was, over her head. Then she held him tightly on the ground. How? She knew Judo. Jiu-jitsu, as judo is sometimes called, means \"muscle science\" in Japanese. The student of judo needs to learn a lot about the body, its bones and muscles. Judo uses a number of \"falls\", \"holds\" and \"throws\". Someone who does not know judo cannot def...\n\nQ: Why does the writer say the world is dangerous?", "options": ["The number of violence and crime is increasing every year.", "Because many people carry guns.", "Because there too many films.", "Because people are not able to defend themselves."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3019, "question": "The findings of a new survey have American professors talking about the good old days--when A's were a lot tougher to earn. Sites like Rate My Professors.com make it easy for students to find a class taught by a professor who is known as an \"easy grader\".A recent survey by Kaplan Test Prep found that 46 percent of the more than 1,200 students polled admitted to using the site for just such a purpose. \"Our research shows that many of today's college students are looking at multiple factors when picking out courses: overall teacher quality that will result in a good learning experience, but also instructors who don't like to award a lot of C's and D's,\" said Jeff Olson, vice president of research at Kaplan Test Prep. \"While it makes sense that students would choose kinder graders, it also he...\n\nQ: The writer tends to    _   .", "options": ["favor easy graders", "see grade inflation as unavoidable", "oppose Kaplan Test Prep", "miss the days when A's were hard to earn"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 555, "question": "EDGEWOOD-Every morning at Dixie Heights High School, customers pour into a special experiment: the district's first coffee shop run mostly by students with special learning needs. Well before classes start, students and teachers order Lattes, Cappuccinos and Hot Chocolates. Then, during the first period, teachers call in orders on their room phones, and students make deliveries. By closing time at 9.20 a.m., the shop usually sells 90 drinks. \"Whoever made the chi tea, Ms. Schatzman says it was good,\" Christy McKinley, a second year student, announced recently, after hanging up with the teacher. The shop is called the Dixie PIT, which stands for Power in Transition. Although some of the students are not disabled, many are, and the PIT helps them prepare for life after high school. They lear...\n\nQ: What is the text mainly about?", "options": ["A best-selling coffee.", "A special educational program.", "Government support for schools.", "A new type of teacher-student relationship."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 951, "question": "You can never be too sure these days in the United States of your neighbours or even your customers! Try to keep a low profile in your neighborhood: don't announce to just about everyone that you are running a home business with thousands of dollars worth of equipment. As much as possible, don't invite clients or visitors to your home. In fact I know of some home-based entrepreneurs who would rather meet their clients in a neutral ground, e.g. the client's office or even Starbucks. There are other ways to keep burglars away from your house. *Keep lights on around your house in the evenings. Light is a natural fright for burglars. *Invest in a security alarm, particularly if your house is located in a remote spot. Security systems can often bring down the cost of your homeowner's insurance ...\n\nQ: All of the following are part of the writer's advice except that the homeowner   _  .", "options": ["buy a security alarm and turn it on in the evening", "fix an extra lock on the door from inside", "have the doors made of solid hardwood or heavy metal", "keep lights on in all rooms to threaten burglars"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2840, "question": "My challenge for you is this: to read a book for 15 minutes every single day for a month. Let me explain a bit, by telling you where the challenge came from. I have many things in common with my dad, like music taste and sense of humor, but sadly reading isn't one of them. I can happily spend a whole day with a book, but my dad can't read a book for longer than about 5 minutes. He reads emails, websites and papers for work, but not books. He's busy so I think sitting down to read for just 15 minutes a day is a good way to relax and to introduce him to reading. My dad is by no means the only person who avoids books. I know lots of people would rather relax on their computers or in front of the TV. Everyone is different and has their own interests, but I think there're lots of benefits to re...\n\nQ: The author writes the text mainly basing on   _  .", "options": ["his personal experience", "some scientific experiments", "his father's personal advice", "knowledge from books"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2687, "question": "Silk production has a long and colourful history unknown to most people. Scientific discoveries have shown that silk production existed in China from around 2500 B.C., although it could be much older. For hundreds of years, China kept the secret of silk to itself as one for the most closely protected secrets in history. Anyone revealing the secret of silkworms or trying to take silkworm eggs out of ancient China was punished by death. At one time silk was reserved only for the Chinese emperor. Gradually, others began wearing silk. In addition to being used for clothing, silk came to have industrial uses in ancient China, something that happened in the West only in modern times. Silk was used to make musical instruments, fishing lines, weapons, ropes and even paper. During the Han Dynasty s...\n\nQ: In what order did silk production spread throughout the world according to the passage?", "options": ["Europe aIndia aKorea aChina.", "China aKorea aIndia aEurope.", "China aIndia aKorea aEurope.", "China aEurope aIndia aKorea."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 219, "question": "Do you find getting up in the morning so difficult that it's painful ? This might be called laziness, but Dr. Kleitman has a new explanation. He has proved that everyone has a daily energy cycle. During the hours when you labour through your work you may say that you're \"hot\". That's true. The time of day when you feel most energetic is when your cycle of body temperature is at its peak . For some people the peak comes during the forenoon. For others it comes in the afternoon or evening No one has discovered why this is so , but it leads to such familiar monologues as : \"Get up, John! You'll be late for work again !\" The possible explanation to the trouble is that John is at his temperature-and -energy peak in the evening. Much family quarrelling ends when husbands and wives realize what t...\n\nQ: What's the best title of the passage?", "options": ["Change Your Habits", "Save Your Energy", "Daily Energy Cycle", "Temperature- and-Energy Peak"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3238, "question": "How can you build more word-of-mouth advertising ? In other words, why would your customers want to talk to their friends about their experience of doing business with you? When you perform your service or deliver your product competently , you are just doing what the customer expects. In order to increase the number of the customers who want to share their good experience with their friends, you must make your service impressive, going beyond what is expected. Recently my daughter Dawn and I had lunch with my team members at the Campbell House. The food and service were truly excellent. My daughter asked for her leftovers to be packed. They were returned to her in aluminum foil shaped like a swan . Guess what she talked about when she got home? How much more do you think it cost the Campb...\n\nQ: By saying \"Answer -- not a cent!\" the author seems to believe that   _  .", "options": ["it is always possible to satisfy all of the customers", "sometimes it is easy to provide a good experience", "most customers are easy to do business with", "the service should be as cheap as possible"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2356, "question": "Driver Wanted Clean driving license . Must be of smart appearance. Age over 25. Apply to : Capes Taxi, 17 Palace Road, Royston. Air Hostesses for International Flights Wanted Applicants must be between 20 and 33 years old. Height: 1.6 m to 1.75 m. Education to GCSE standard. Two languages. Must be able to swim. Apply to: Recruitment office, Southern Airlines, Heathrow Airport West. HR 37 KK. Teachers Needed For private language school. Having college education. Teaching experience unnecessary. Apply to: The Director of Studies, Instant Languages Ltd. 279 Canal Street, Royston....\n\nQ: Which of the following is not mentioned in the three advertisements?", "options": ["Marriage.", "Male or female.", "Education.", "Working experience."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 869, "question": "To Whom It May Concern: prefix = st1 /Chengdu #7 High School is proud to send an Odyssey of the MindTeam to World Competition this year. They competed inShanghaifor the National Competition and were selected to go to World. The World Competition will be held at the University of Maryland in theUnited Statesat the end of May. Odyssey of the Mind is a creative problem-solving competition. Teams of up to seven students will solve a complex problem using innovative ideas and materials. They will be judged on originality in three separate categories. Odyssey of the Mind competitions emphasize team work and creative \"out of the box\" solutions. The strength of this program is that the solutions are the work of the students only - neither coaches nor parents are allowed input. During the competiti...\n\nQ: What's the purpose for the writer to write such a passage?", "options": ["To introduce the Odyssey of the Mind team in ChengduNo 7 High School.", "To ask for possible donation support.", "To tell the readers something about Chengdu No 7 High School.", "To inform \"To Whom It May Concern\"."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1448, "question": "When I was 16 years old and in foster care in Tennessee, people told me I was unadoptable. But I desperately wanted a family. I sought the help of a judge, even the commissioner of the Department of Children's Services, and was adopted just a week before my 18th birthday. We have a lot to be grateful for and this holiday season let's not forget about the more than 415,000 youth in foster care especially older youth. These youth are the most likely to get overlooked for adoption, but they shouldn't be. They need and deserve a family just as much as young children do. Making an older youth a part of your family can bring just as much a joy as adopting a baby or a younger child--without all the diapers and potty training. My adoption was life changing and probably the best thing that ever hap...\n\nQ: What contributes to the author's feeling that she can't imagine being alone in the world.", "options": ["The family's giving the author a Mickey Mouse as a gift.", "The author's spending her Thanksgiving with her extended family for 17 years.", "The mother's failing to attend the author's wedding ceremony for her severe disease.", "The family's always sharing happiness and sorrow with her."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3180, "question": "NOT all math skills are learned in the classroom. Some of them come naturally. Consider the split-second calculations you make when you estimate the number of empty seats on the school bus or the number of cookies in a cookie jar. These estimates can often be done without counting. That's because humans are born with the ability to closely guess the number of items in a group. Researchers call this ability a person's \"number sense\". To see how a person's inborn number sense might be linked to mathematical performance in the classroom, psychologist Justin Halberda and his colleagues from Johns Hopkins University in prefix = st1 /Baltimore,USran some tests. The scientists asked 64 14-year-olds to look at images of yellow and blue dots that flashed on a computer screen for a fraction of a sec...\n\nQ: What is the result of Justin Halberda's tests?", "options": ["Students who did well in the tests also did well in math exams.", "One cannot be successful in math if he has a well number sense.", "One who has a strong number sense can not do math well.", "One should do a lot of math homework if he wants to have a number sense."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2264, "question": "There is an English saying that goes, \"he who laughs last, laughs the hardest.\" High School Musical star and teen heartthrob Zac Efron is laughing a lot these days. As a young boy, Efron was picked on in school because he was always the smallest in his class and teased because he had a big space between his teeth. In the sixth grade, Efron's basketball team made it to the league championships. In double overtime , with three seconds left, he rebounded the ball and passed it to the wrong team! They scored and his team lost the game. But history, as they say, is a thing of the past. Now at 21, Efron is one of People magazine's 100 Most Beautiful People, graces the cover of Entertainment Weekly, Hollywood's most influential magazine, and is traveling the world promoting the third High School ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is True according to the passage?", "options": ["Zac Efron was laughed at because he was the most foolish guy in the class", "Zac Efron is promoting his fourth High School Musical film in the world.", "He once helped the other team win a match when he was playing basketball.", "In his growing process to be a famous actor, his mother played a key part."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2877, "question": "A 56-year-old Canadian man who left home after his business went bankrupt completed an 11-year walk around the world on Sunday, and told a crowd of well-wishers his new goal was to promote peace. Jean Beliveau -- who arrived to a hero's welcome in Montreal from loved ones, lawmakers and supporters -- said his \"real aim \" was to advise Canada and other governments to build \"ministries of peace.\" \"We are all different, and that is what is beautiful about life on Earth -- our different color1s, different beliefs, different political systems,\" he said. \"Those are all musical notes... we must create harmony from them, create a common tune,\" an emotional Beliveau told the crowd gathering at city hall in the old part of the city. Beliveau left Montreal on the day of his 45th birthday -- August 18...\n\nQ: Many people took part in the celebration to welcome Beliveau's return EXCEPT   _  .", "options": ["his mother", "his girlfriend", "his children", "his former wife"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 889, "question": "If you're one of the 13 million Americans still struggling to find a job, or wanting to change jobs, a lot of your applications are probably being swallowed up by the \"the black hole.\" That's when you send in a job application and never receive any follow-up from the company.In fact, only 25 out of 100 applications ever get looked at by companies. Now, a remarkable new service is helping job seekers instantly track almost every application they submit so they actually know what's going on.It's called Start Wire. corn and it lets job seekers track their applications and find out whether or not their applications have been reviewed, dismissed, or are still being considered. How does it work? When you fill out a job application via a company website, you'll typically get an auto confirmation ...\n\nQ: If you want to use Start Wire first you should   _", "options": ["make a call to the website", "get access to some employers", "register an account without payment", "email the company you will apply to"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 950, "question": "You can never be too sure these days in the United States of your neighbours or even your customers! Try to keep a low profile in your neighborhood: don't announce to just about everyone that you are running a home business with thousands of dollars worth of equipment. As much as possible, don't invite clients or visitors to your home. In fact I know of some home-based entrepreneurs who would rather meet their clients in a neutral ground, e.g. the client's office or even Starbucks. There are other ways to keep burglars away from your house. *Keep lights on around your house in the evenings. Light is a natural fright for burglars. *Invest in a security alarm, particularly if your house is located in a remote spot. Security systems can often bring down the cost of your homeowner's insurance ...\n\nQ: Some home-based entrepreneurs don't invite clients to their home   _  .", "options": ["to enjoy convenience outside their home", "for reasons of their property safety", "not to let others know their business", "in order to avoid being seen by burglars"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2272, "question": "According to a famous optical expert, Alexander, who recently visited Shanghai, the developed countries in Europe and America have made rules that children must wear resinous glasses instead of the traditional glasses made of glass. This is because the glass glasses are more likely to do harm to children's eyesight. Alexander pointed out: wearing the right glasses as soon as possible is still the best way to cure and put right children's eyesight problems. In America and Japan the resinous glasses have taken up 80 percent of the glasses market. And some European countries and America have made it a law that children, teenagers and drivers must wear resinous glasses. Now, about 10 million children in China have different eyesight problems and they need timely treatment. But still, too many ...\n\nQ: This news article mainly wants to tell us   _  .", "options": ["Alexander visited China and introduced a new type of glasses", "we should wear resinous glasses instead of glass glasses", "resinous glasses are popular in Europe and America", "glasses can be made of other materials instead of glass"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2204, "question": "The picture-like island is rich in scenic beauty. Barbados sightseeing is a photographer's dream that comes true with numbers of natural wonders, breathtaking scenic views, attractive gardens and miles of white, sandy beaches. There's so many things to see and to do, as you check out some of the places of interest on the island. Historical Appeal Experience Full of historical appeal you'll love the impressive collection of beautiful great houses, landmarks, old churches, and traditional ancient houses some of which may date back to the 16th century. Historic Bridgetown, over 375 years old, capital of Barbados, is located with its color1ful fishing boats and splendid yachts ( ) . Check out the Barbados National and see some of the island's most beautiful homes. Nature Charm Enjoyment Nature...\n\nQ: Which of the followings is the sightseeing of Historic Bridgetown?", "options": ["Traditional houses and rocky caves.", "Beautiful houses and nature paths.", "Old churches and splendid yachts.", "Landmarks and tropical plants."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 168, "question": "Directions: Read the following passage. The passage is followed by several questions or unfinished statements. For each of them there are four choices marked A,B,C and D. Choose the one that fits best according to the information given in the passage. It may be open to discussion which city is the most beautiful in the world. But in terms of \" the most livable\", Melbourne has ranked top in a survey done by the Economist Intelligence Unit (EIU) in August. In fact, four cities Down Under are among the top ten most livable cities. The climate in Australia is warm and mild, particularly in major coastal cities. As a result, people spend much time outdoors. They go to the beach, to the countryside, or play sports outdoors in fields. Take Melbourne for example. The city features many open green ...\n\nQ: What can be concluded from the article?", "options": ["Melbourne is the most culturally diverse city in the world.", "The majority of Australians are fascinated with sports and art.", "The Australian government tries to make immigrants feel at home.", "Australians are considered to be the most patriotic in the world."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3348, "question": "In cities with rent control, the city government sets the maximum rent that a landlord can charge for an apartment. Supporters of rent control argue that it protects people who are living in apartments. Their rent cannot increase; therefore, they are not in danger of losing their homes. However, the critics say that after a long time, rent control may have negative effects. Landlords know that they cannot increase their profits . Therefore, they invest in other businesses where they can increase their profits. They do not invest in new buildings which would also be rent - controlled. As a result, new apartments are not built. Many people who need apartments cannot find any. According to the critics, the end result of rent control is a shortage of apartments in the city. Some theorists argu...\n\nQ: According to the critics, rent control_.", "options": ["will always benefit those who rent apartments", "is unnecessary", "will bring negative effects in the long run", "is very necessary"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 453, "question": "No one is sure how the ancient Egyptians built the pyramids near Cairo. But a new study suggests they used a little rock'n'roll. Long-ago builders could have attached wooden poles to the stones and rolled them across the sand, the scientists say. \"Technically, I think what they're proposing is possible,\" physicist Daniel Bonn said. People have long puzzled over how the Egyptians moved such huge rocks. And there's no obvious answer. On average, each of the two million big stones weighed about as much as a large pickup truck. The Egyptians somehow moved the stone blocks to the pyramid site from about one kilometer away. The most popular view is that Egyptian workers slid the blocks along smooth paths. Many scientists suspect wokers first would have put the blocks on sleds . Then they would h...\n\nQ: What is the text mainly about ?", "options": ["An experiment on ways of moving blocks to the pyramid site.", "An argument about different methods of moving blocks to the pyramid site.", "An application of the method of moving blocks to the pyramid site.", "An introduction to a possible new way of moving blocks to the pyramid site."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3170, "question": "\"Our aim is to take our art to the world and make people understand what it is to move,\" said David Belle, the cofounder of parkour . Do you love running? It is a good exercise, yet many people find it boring. But what if making your morning jog a creative one?Like jumping from walls and over gaps and ground rolls? Just like the James Bond in the movie Casino Royale? Bond jumps down from a roof to a windowsill and then runs several blocks over _ on the way. It is just because of Bond's wonderful performances that the sport has become popular worldwide. Yes, that's parkour, an extreme street sport aimed at moving from one point to another as quickly as possible, getting over all the obstacles in the path using only the abilities of the human body. Parkour is considered an extreme sport. As ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the philosophy of parkour?", "options": ["Sports and extremes.", "Excitement and popularity.", "Dreams and success.", "Determination and freedom."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1647, "question": "An old friend from California called from the airport to tell me that he had arrived. I was not able to leave the office, but I had made plans for his arrival. After explaining where my new house was, I told him that I had left the key under the doormat . Since I knew it would be pretty late before I could get home, I suggested that he make himself at home and help himself to anything that was in the refrigerator . Two hours later my friend phoned me from the house. At the moment, he said, he was listening to some of my records after having had a delicious meal. Now, he said, he was drinking a glass of orange juice. When I asked him if he had had any difficulty finding the house, he answered that the only problem was that he had not been able to find the key under the doormat, but luckily,...\n\nQ: My friend telephoned me two hours later   _   .", "options": ["from my home", "at the airport", "in his office", "from my neighbor's house"], "answer": 3}]